Welcome to the Python tutorial today we're going to talk about a function in Python a function is a
block of code that is used to perform one task.
We can repeat the function many times and spit out requirement which means that we define a function
once and a user can use over and over again.
So is call a function in Python.
Now I'm going to explain to you how to use the function function in Python.
You do fine using the word B.
And after that keyword we write the name of the function with fantasies.
I tried the name of the function with it is after and Carlon to get inside the function.
And now I'm going to simply print a string which is hello and in the next line put it down.
I used to get out of the function when I hit enter.
You can see if it goes out of the function.
So here the new line is started.
So now I'm going to call the function to call the function.
We simply write the name of the function to know the name of the function followed by better places
and in parenthesis we can place any argument.
So here I don't put any argument and will simply call the function in then me.
The result is string which means that when we call that function this name the function is called.
And this is printed in output.
So these are all about the only way defining the function.