This to do it you we're going to discuss some argument which are used in function.
So the first argument is required argument.
These are the main boss to function of correct order which means that the number of argument in the
function call sort of matched exactly to the function definition.
So it is necessary to get the exact value in the function call and the function definition.
So let's understand this simple example here.
I'm going to create a function after that I'll explain you the required argument.
So for that if you use a keyboard.
Hello I'm going to simply print the string Hello world.
After that I'll simply tear down this function and outside the function to simply call this function
by me.
So we'll get the result.
Hello Will we get the result.
Hello world.
So where do you get it.
Why the argument inside this function like X and we did not pass anything inside this calling function.
Then we'll get the argument error so we can see quite the argument as it is shown.
So here I'm going to simply pass a variable x here.
I we learned this morning we'll get the.
Hello world we get the result.
X is not defined so for that we can define X equal to then we'll get there.
Hello world what is functioning correctly.
These are all about the quarte argument.
Insert the function the next argument is the key word argument.
It is related to a function call.
So then call the function.
We have to identify the argument by the bad name.
So let's understand from the example here Anglo-Dutch simply create a function named hello and instead
the parent has put x.
After that I will simply print the value of X let me call the function here.
I'm going to simply call the function by the name hello and insert the function and put 23.
So this tree is passed to the variable x and the X is printed.
So when you get there is an entity.
So what is a good argument.
This function.
So I think I already said when to call the function we have to identify this argument by that by and
with the name.
So I'll put X to and granted 3.
So this value of going to 3 is identified by the bet and we don't name x.
So this gives you an argument so is all about.
Your argument in function.
The next argument is a default argument.
It is the argument that defines the value of value is not provided in the function.
So let's understand a simple example.
I'm going to get a simple function.
Hello is that the function.
Simply put X in the right loop.
After that it is simply print the value of x and y.
So I'll try the function to simply call this function by the name hello and insert the function will
give to them and we don't get 3 in the 45.
So within this month you will get the exact result which is 23 and 45.
So what does that do for an argument.
So then we remove this value from the calling function and would insert the definition of the function.
So so what bystander's it will firstly copy the value guaranteed to insert this variable x.
So then within this model we will get the exact result.
We just don't want to fight.
So these are all about a default argument.
The next argument is the variable length argument these type of argument is used when we define the
function and we don't know how many argument we are going to parse in certain function which means that
the perimeter and the argument both of very As But our requirement.
So let us understand to a simple example.
First you have to create a function but that would be and name the function.
Hello.
And instead the function parent is put to Mr X and then and before and I'll put a stick mark this denoted
that here you pass as many value.
Insert this.
Bette Midler.
So first you have to put in the belly of.
So as to return the function and simply call it function by using.
And here I put.
Well so this 12 is complete good this variable x and x is printed.
Hey we get this.
Well and now I'm going to give some different value and insert the function with attractive 4 4 5 and
6.
So here we have three values for this variable.
And so this TV news is stored in the variable.
And so I'm going to simply get the value from that and using a for loop for B.
And I would simply put in value be we this more to be able to get that IZARD Well and after that we
will prevent you from the variable x.
We just turned it for 6 and 45.
So here this variable lenth argument is two values and the variable length Bellamy is.
And we can pass different vendors.
Day 6 again.
Certainly 18N this on the values is taught instead is very well.
Because these a strict MA which do not.
The bill passes different values and many believe in this very well.
So these are all about a variable argument function.