This to do you we're going to discuss what is possible and what is passed by reference.
So let us start with a pass by value.
So when you pass of value what we are doing is that we get it a copy of that variable and passes to
the function.
Suppose we created a variable x that will do fine outside the function and when we passed the variable
x occurred to 5 inside the function then we are not passing the actual value.
We are only passing the operator value here.
I opened up can script and now I'm going to execute a simple example by passing.
Then you insert the function.
So for that be a booklet of function.
So here I put a keyword in creating a function and now and give the name of the function which is hello
and instead this parent is I'll.
But don't exit after that and put Conan to get inside this function and will simply print the value
of x.
After that it will be done this.
So here are funkiness completed.
And now we have to create a variable x which are positive inside this function.
So for that and put X equal to B.
And after the next line I'm going to simply call this function by using the name Heno and insert this
function and put the argument x which is BOCES in this function.
So when we execute this model forget trivial Tartine because Harry Potter is a valuable Tartine.
So what happens when you exit 45
Hedi we get the new result which is exactly two point five.
One more thing.
It will bring about a new X and then we'll see what happens.
So we get all these new leads and we just harden.
So now I'm going to explain you the boss may Velu in this function.
So here first we create a variable x 19 and we just bodged to our function.
Hello.
So any pass this video will actually do.
Tiding then what we are doing here is just passing the copy of this variable which is x.
So then we actually do 14 in the function then it will not reflect back here altered the function because
here we just only passing the copied value not the actual value.
But this is the method to passing the value into this function.
So these are all about a possible value.
Now let's move to the next topic which is the pass by reference when we pass something why it happens.
So what we are doing is parsing the object itself or we can say you passing the or isn't variable.
We are not copying the variable we just passed the variable in that function.
So any change in the object or variable in the function then those changes are reflected back to the
actual variable.
Now let us understand to a simple example here and could execute a simple example of pass by and I-phones.
So first we have to create a function using the key word B.
And after that I'll put the name of the function which is hello.
And instead the identity is kept up but excellent.
And after that colon forget the function and I will simply print the value of variable x.
So had we done this function you don't keyword.
So this function is completed and after that the appropriate variable response inside the function.
So here I am going to create a variable in firstling which is the.
So here I created a list instead of variable.
So here we have 4 item in the list.
And these four items are boxed in so this function to bust the list.
Instead this function we have to call this function by that name.
Hello.
And here I put a two boxes in this function table and this model
so heavy get the result of this list.
So now I'm who next been you.
What is a pass by reference in this function.
Now I'm going to join the list inside this function here.
I put it in the X and instead the square Bechard album zero which is the index value of this list and
hit it.
And so here the list is updated by the index value of zero.
Well now I wonder simply print the updated list help me get the result updated.
You can see the index position as 0 is genius to you.
Now I'm going to simply print the value of list outside the function here.
So here we get the same result with which is outside the function.
So there's no difference between the list inside the function and the outside the function because then
we passed the list in the function we just passed the actual list not the copied list then whenever
we change anything in the list that it will reflect back outside the function.
So these all about are passed by reference in a function.