Hello guys in the previous tutorial we have seen how to execute a simple hello world program.
And in this tutorial we learn something about variables.
So what is mean by a variable.
Yes.
OK.
It is nothing but a storage location location where your doctor is taught you can say whatever type
of value we need.
And a reasonable value can be changed on assignment dynamically and run them during program execution.
So how to create a variable in Python.
So these are the syntax of creating a variable and by then it was nothing but for example let's see
and let's say this following statement We are creating a variable name called Word and assigning it
value Hello World to is variable called what.
When you bring this war as we had in the previous two areas you'll get hello last spring day.
So let's check out some examples.
Problematically inter-communal as well as scripts.
And as of now let's check.
All right let's see how this variable declaration is done in other programming languages like Java
here.
Equal to same is used to assign values to variables.
Let's dig into the construction
here.
We have created a variable called member variable and assigned a value of 10 to this variable and the
dotted line as in.
This is the most important part.
In other type of in other languages.
Now the number of variables stores only in these are values in it because we have declared this number
variable of God or God.
Similarly in case of other statements by examples string available we have created a string variable
and assign the value lowballed to the string variable often datatype as string and hence string variable
stores only a string that they want.
Similarly with the case of floor variable.
But in case of Python there is no need of declaration.
I mean there is no need to be clear what I mean the Dobber types of variables.
In brief what I mean there is no declaration of variables neither.
And you can get them McAlary at runtime in the program do what what I mean.
OK here you go.
In case of Job and C other programming languages you need be explicit Lydick and declare war type of
data.
You need to storing the variable.
It means a variable declaration isn't needed according to data.
As we have discussed in this example Hensick is manageable.
Declare together datatype in case of other programming languages.
But as we have discussed in case of Biden there is no need of explicit declaration of types.
When grading articulating declaring the variables we'll see that in the following example.
Let's take this statement.
We have declared.
We remove all independent variable and assign a value to it.
And similarly with the other variables in case substring variable we have created.
We have as same as drink on hello world this being the table and the value of one 20.00 is bloviated.
So how does Python know what type of data datatype to be assigned to this particular variable.
So that's an interesting question and interesting future feature of Biden.
So by itself I Uniface what type of datatype it garding I mean according to the value you are saying
to this variable dynamically entered into runtime.
For example you have assigned it then value is indeed available and during runtime during the execution
of the program by done.
I didn't deifies another day of this.
These are valuable.
Based on this based on the data you have assigned to this particular variable.
Similarly in case of the string variable by Biden identifies the datatype of this string variable as
screen based on the value you have assigned to the weather string.
By then I didn't deface the data date as string.
Similarly with variables flawed variable and list variable.
Let's implement these examples programmatically to look into that and also to restrict open the terminal
and open the to
OK we are into an interpreter.
Let's create some variables with the different bands.
OK here we have created five variables a b c d e f and assign different dagger values to it in guess
of and we have a sign.
And in this one too.
And hello world.
In case of we have assigned a string called Hello World to be.
And similarly with other variable C D E F and F F E and D These are the list.
And this was the study done it up and it was a double decker.
Don't worry about this we'll begin to win.
And then in the next two years for this kind of data types.
OK.
So let's bring these variables.
Up by print all the values of the variables that are stored in their memory locations.
OK.
So you can able to identify.
I mean you can able to ask them what type of data at particular value storing it by using a function
called type.
For example let's take the variable.
You want to check what was the exact datatype of that particular variable.
You can you can do so by using a function call type.
So you can able to see here the datatype of the particular variable was in.
Since you have assigned an and indiscernible value do that.
Similarly we can to check the other day of all the other remaining variables
B.
And it was stream.
Since we have a same as string value in the debatable B be similarly beginning to check the types of
all the remaining datatypes.
There you go the dagger type of see was flawed.
The dagger type of D was elist the datatype of he was a dictionary the datatype of a variable.
It was double.
So in this way you can able to declare the variables and assign different types of different Dagar type
of variables to that particular variables and Biden doesn't rate stuff identifying the datatype of that
particular variable.
And you can also you can also be able to check what type of data a particular variable stored by using
it by Done builtin function called Type.
And one more important thing was during declaring or initialization of the variables you need to take
it off not using the by default.
What all get here Python comes with a list of keywords that can be used out of the box from Python.
Let's see what other list of key words that are available from Biden.
So these are the list of words that comes with Python out of the box.
And as break except So when you are declaring a particular variable b I mean be careful not to use.
I mean every word from one of these alist if you lose Joe Biden will 20 runs off you.
You cannot use that.
Let's check this
see you see.
Biden has told.
You're gonna be able to use that.
And it was and it was indexed in maliks index because you aren't able to use the default Python keyboard
as a variable here.
So Python knows what type of data source innervated been doing based on the type of value you assign
to it.
In Python you can also do some multiple assignments multiple times.
OK so you can understand by example
from this statement We have created three variables a b c a daytime and assigned a value one to it.
So this is called multiple assignment.
We can assign a value to multiple variables and then in Python.
Similarly you can able to check what type of data it has to as I have previously if it was and when
you check this type for other variables B and C and the same type was in.
And also you can you can both forms of operations on the table whaleboat if you would like for example
create an indecent variable.
Now you can able to pull from some of them into corporations like plus minus in India on the table variables
that we have declared or let's do that
Deeble we have the output of 30 when we added been we added that able to whaleboat and then important
point to note here was you can do or even book from a domestic operations on the same Dagar variables
for example get into variable and into variable too are the variables of God today.
In this sense we have a saying and then to each other in these sets you cannot perform on them and operations
on two different other for example you can't add and in these are variable and a string variable.
Let's take that
one.
Now you can perform our domestic operations on the table on these two variables since there are variables
of two different data types.
Sorry.
Actually you need to agree.
You need to get a string variable with a string value and so that it will become fingertip.
Let's take what we have.
Study so we have a S.O.P But let's check the value of string variable
element.
Let's try to add these two.
No.
There you go.
Biden has trial and error saying that your answer put it all right.
I mean you can't add two different names in this that and string.
So this was an error of which was quite a bit.
There are many types of it passing by then.
I mean which comes out of the box you can able to loan them in our future to the audience.
So domestic operations can be bought from the same data type variables but not different variables.
You can you can pull some different data mining operations like multiplication addition and subtraction
etc..
Ok guys that's all for this video and I hope you enjoy it and learn something about the variables and
variable types and multiple assignments and checking just checking the actual datatype of a particular
variable you have created.
Let's do something some something important.
I mean let's learn something important stuff in our next video.
We don't yes.
Thanks thanks very much guys.