Heidi folks in this video to do real good looks and by that I mean for Luban by them.
So what is and what actually is Luby looping does nothing with the mechanism of it written with sequels
or headaches which are nothing but string list double and dict.
So what does it need to be looping is required to the beat and execution of a block of code.
Is that a number of times.
I like to do an example for each and every sequence of a day.
But for example string list double date before that this was indexable.
What does it mean was Biden ablaze eloping.
I mean by then blaze be on each and every item of sequence stack and assigns that particular item to
this variable called 8.
And we are going to pin that variable.
All right.
Let's open the Python interpreter and write give you an example for each and the
right time and by the end of I think you example we do a lot of text.
One is a string and one is a list.
And he said of your seven string.
All right.
Now I want to bring each and every character of this string variable.
So initially we have declared a variable called string variable and assign a value string to this variable.
Let's print each and every character by using for loop in Python from.
We have the international force base and then
right.
So this was the indented output of printing each and every Goetic separately by using the final look
let's apply the same logic.
I mean the same follow on the list that it
right we have initialized a variable call list variable and assign a datatype of a list with two items
in it and which has a list of two items in it.
If you've been pleased to be able
allright oops be vulgar to call me that.
Now let's bring Duguay.
There you go.
So we have two items in this list.
Let's play the for loop on this.
But Igla list available
now they intended should be Halo and war should be been updated as the two items independently in the
list.
All right.
So this is all about playing follow up on different data digs invite them to rebuild this Valo with
another function call arranged range invite that range is nothing with the building by that function
which is to the degree to list stuff.
Nimbus made a predefined them but even that function.
Let's see an example for the
little Pindi to see what other elements in that particular area.
All right.
So it has created a numbers from 0 9 with this built in function let being that each and every variable
each and every number independently
they will.
So this is all about applying for lobes are not a description of a for loop in Python.
Thanks guys.
We'll try to do another topic in our next video.
Thanks very much.