Hire one.
Now let's have a look at why those invited and why loop statement in Python programming language repeatedly
executes that statement.
As long as a given condition is true and the syntax of why loop is like this.
Why then the expression
statements
and you might be wondering what his boss was eased as statement.
Which do nothing.
So if we want to declare a function all we want to write a law and if we want to do nothing then we
can just use this POS like here and now I will get rid of this because I just want to do something in
this Lew and so that he'll leave statement.
Maybe a single statement for a block of statements and the expression on the condition may be any expression
and true is any known zero value.
The loop iterates while the condition is true and when the condition becomes false the program control
passes to the line immediately following the loop.
Now let's have a look at the flow diagram of why this is the flow diagram of why.
And here we will check for the expression here and if it is true then the conditional called will get
executed and after that we will check for the result and if the condition is again true then conditional
code will be executed.
And this will continue to do until the condition here becomes thoughts and if the condition is force
the program through will go to the very next line of code.
Here we keep going all the while loop is that the loop might not.
And when the condition is disturbed and so does force the loop more the baby skipped and the first statement
after the while loop will be executed so that the Y is also our last entry loop.
This is the condition here is false at the beginning says.
Then the program flow will not get into the loop.
And likewise all the half and exceed lobola so that this card do a loop and above the while loop.
We will be discussing in upcoming new deals.
So now let's have a look good an example.
So for that I will get rid of this loads and I want to declare a variable count equals zero then I just
want to look through it with an expression
count less than 5.
I just want to bring the count and after that I just won't be sure that the way you get exceeded.
And for that I also want to bring a string which is just like good bye or something like that.
And I just want to get rid of this boss here and I would just save this and let's go to the terminal
and run this program by David IDN.
What's happening or just I just for go to increment.
That's why it's happening.
And it is an infinite loop.
Seems the ground is equal to zero.
And the why can these less than five it will always bring the.
And in order to get out of the loop just get on board and see.
And it shows keyboard interrupted.
Just go to the code find out something like gun equals going plus one then it will show the actual doesn't
like this zero up before and when will the count equals five.
The condition becomes false and this will get out of this loop.
And the problem can really go to the next line and it will print goodbye.
And in the first case we had a sign it was only an infinite loop because of the condition inside this
White loop.
These are the two like I want or something like that.
So any non-zero value inside this way can make an infinite loop.
So that's all about y loops and by then.
So keep watching.
Thank you.