Welcome to the Python tutorial today we are going to talk about more youth in python modules in Python
simply python files with extension which contains sort of function which means that your model file
will always contain different function and these functions are used in another file.
We use them more.
You could break down large put them into small manageable files so if we define our most use function
in a module and we import it by using import keyword.
So now let's move to the examples of models here.
I just opened a folder with the empty folder and now I'm going to get a module file in this folder for
that
engaged module file which is another way.
And now I'm going to create a function that is more dual.
So for that we have to use the Internet and give the name of the function we just press and insert the
function as simply pre-testing we do.
I from what do
they serve this function.
And now I'm going to create another file which is or is not a file.
You can give any name to this but it is a file here.
I just get rid of modify and or interface.
Or is what I used to do.
Or you can say that all the function from this one do we just do another beba.
And now I'm going to use import keyword to import the function from this more do so simply import the
module first.
We just do not and this is our name of the model.
And after that I will simply call the function by using the name of the model which is doing not are
first we simply run this model.
We get the result I am from want do.
So this is a method when we call the models in sympathetically.
So we have another method to import Ahmadu in different directory.
So if you want to access the module file in any degrees or defended agree then we have to create the
model in the site because this site is located in our Python installed dedicatory.
I'm going to open up by Tanstaafl that actually here in local type See your local FC user name of the
user in standard Aberdare dong loken for that program.
Then by then are defined to do here.
We just open up by to install dedicatory and insert that we have a folder called Live and inside the
lib rehabber site packages folder.
So here I just will Burnetts I begged this folder and instead I'm going to create a module file.
So here and what I viewed or more do I mean
more to do first don't be very
Instead this modified and when to be a simple function which you done.
Mr.
side
is this function.
Instead it's more do.
So are we ever more do you more do it faster.
And instead the more do we have a function name.
Hello and now I'm going to call this more to do from another that.
So here we go.
The dog went for dinner and now I want to.
What he's in five which is right.
More Dieu.
Don't you worry.
And incentives what is.
I'm going to call them what do you want.
You will import more and do
what you want doing first.
And now I'm going to call a function which we have created in them what do you
have in this.
What do they get that isn't it just from sight bankers.
So this hour another method when you call them or do something and then that is the one more thing.
When you create a model in our site packages then you can call them model in any day in your computer.
So this is all about more do in by Python.