Welcome to the Python tutorial today we're going to talk about string in Python.
String is a set of character or we can say that the string is a collection of character represented
in a single court order double code.
So now let us understand to a simple example.
Here I open up by person and now I'm going to get as good some example after that I explain you
personally.
They presented a string and double called So here we get the result which is a string value.
So now again I'm going to give the same well-doing single code.
So we get the same value as we get in the previous value.
So these are all about string.
Now I'm going to explain you some method which are used in string for the first method is the capitalized
third capitalized method rewritten the same history but the only difference is that it will return a
capital as the first character.
So postulate execute this method
so firstly you have to create a string for their Hello world
and I'm going to call the capitalized method.
You don't capitalize.
So here we get the result.
Hello world.
You can see the difference between this and the word and this Helliwell where the edge is capital.
And the answer is hello.
That is a small capitalized method.
Let's give you the first character in capital.
So it is all about capitalized method.
The second method is the method gone method is used to a character inside the collection of actors for
that when to give the.
Well Lou at the end.
Hello.
That's what we do.
And again I'm going to print the value your door.
See you in the to count and which will leave you up to code and giving it the.
So here we get the result.
Do you mean that it is to insert this whole string here.
Easy ones.
And the second is here.
So these are all out to count.
My third gunmetal will simply count the character.
The next method is a Find method find a method used to find the index position of character.
So now execute this program and assigning a value which is owned by Stanistreet and when to find be
inserted by Peniston.
So you don't find earned human activity.
So here we get the result too.
So detector is in the index position of two.
So P is inverted 0.
Why isn't one.
And Deeson do.
So the find character will give you the next position on the character.
The next method is alphanumeric method.
The alphanumeric method will return either true or false.
If your string contents alphanumeric values are unknown.
So for that I'm getting ready as I need to string which is hello after that and then to give some dessert
after that again and when to write hello or now to print the alphanumeric values so that you don't I
s d l and you m.
So here we go to the desert to which Muenster our history contains the alphabet X as well as disease.
Well you said indeed the Velu.
So these are all about alphanumeric Billoo the next method is is Alfar method that is open method will
return you either true or false.
If your story contains the alphabet or not.
So for that I'm when to say if I were adding value which just hello or not and print this condition
your daughter is ill be it is alpha.
So here we go.
No.
2.
So if I if I'm going to give the hello with one two three and deliver a new it can simply give you the
fourth
because these are strong.
Also condoms are indeed available.
So these are all about or is Ulfar method the next method is a digital method deject method will give
you either true or false.
Depend upon your history contains some character or some business.
So for that when to initially give a certain good 3:03 for desert and not ending up in the condition
your daughter is did it.
So here we go and that was all because I was in Grenadines only a digital value.
So these is all about the digital method.
The next method is lenth my third lenth and a third will give you the length of characters.
Hayse the string are now and when to print the length of character and and and in.
So here we get the result 13.
So here we count 1 2 3 4 5 6 and the virus is 7 8 9 10.
Well today it is all about the lenth character.
The next method is a the method no one method will give you the lower value.
If you give some random characters.
So if I'm going to give some relief as we are I
hello world blues get Pradel and all characters are small if you play the hello way
Dorte or even the odd.
So how do we get the desired all the characters in the smaller to even the Doebbler is also a smaller
dose.
So it is all about the legitimatized the next Metallica.
But I guess my third guess method really give you the non-job character which means that it will give
you the capital value.
So if came the same hello world string and green the relevant upright
so how do we get the results.
All the actor in the capital form.
So it is all about the apprentice method.
The next method is a step Kismat a third step this method is used to Sebha the string.
It means that if you give the small actor it was simply swept into the capital character or if you give
the capital act it would convert it into the small character.
So for that hearing will give the character well character Hello world and now and then to exit this
print or now you is done with ISTEP case.
Harry get all look at it in a small letter.
So if we give the we're in
small letters
or in this don't ask is SEPIC here we get all the character in character form.
So this is all about the swep guess method.
The next method is Mxs method Mxs method will do don't you.
The maximum is a drink actor in the collection of character to be considered the stream.
So for that equal to
Hello World.
Now I'm going to exit the next get it to X and so heavy get the result that gives the largest character
in this string.
So this is all about the next guy.
Excellent.
I didn't say that Mxs method.
The next method is a min method.
When method is used to get a minimum correct value in say the string.
So for that I'm going to give some.
Doing well which is by 10 and I'm going to print them minimum leverage and Min.
So here we get the desired edge.
So the minimum character insert this is doing.
So these are all about the min method the last method is the placement third placement third this in
blue.
He plays that character and he's really greater screen named by them.
Now I'm going to replace the Python for you don't
please and we've got a place to be today.
So the b's the on list character of a new.
And does the new value have a word that is a limit to the Zayton.
Which means that B is the best way to read it.
The best way.
So it is all about the history.
In Python.