Welcome to the white industry today I'm going to show you how to use my Esquith.
It might come so before getting started.
We have to install some packages or we can say some software to use might as well be fun.
So here we have some software.
So the first one is all mine.
A square server community.
The second one is you might as well work bench.
And the third one is the my Esquith Brighton connector so the code one which isn't my Esquith connector
used to connect to you BI Can problem with my squill database so let's move to that installation process.
So here I just open a composer and insert but you can type my Esquith dot com slash downloads after
that.
Just scroll down and go to the last one which is my s well Community Edition.
Just click on community.
So here we have some software which is in my as well to the server my squill cluster.
So first you have to download them might as well come in to the server.
Yes click on that.
Here we have MY as well coming into a server.
Just scroll down and now you can select your operating system because I have a Mac operating system.
Just click on download button which is the first one.
So you just click on download.
So here you can see we have to log in or sign up for download this software but we have another link
which is not text.
Just started my download.
So just click on there.
So here you can see the dotted boxes.
So here you can see the download process is running.
So it will take some time.
So I just skip the video.
So here you can see the download process is completed and now here we might as well come into the server.
So now let's move to the second download which is my screen workbench for this.
Go back to your download page.
We just might as well computer downloads after that just to scroll down.
So here we go.
Might as well the workbench just click on that.
So here we have a donor to my Escorial work bench.
Now just click on your add on and what can we do here.
After that just click on No tanks.
Just don't get to my workbench.
So here you can see that the process is started.
So it will take some time.
The puzzle is completed.
So here we can see might School of work workbench which is in Pompadours DMD.
So now let's move to the last installation which is my as well by 10 connector.
So just go to the donor or the
click gone and addition the third leg on my as well connectors.
So here we have so many connectors which is going to ODBC connect and that and connected G.
So connected that is useful Java.
After that we have a connector says no Dodi's.
We just knew after that we have to connect those less by default just less Spuyten.
So here we have a download page for a practice less.
You can just scroll down.
Slickville operating system.
So here I just use that font independent.
And after that I just click on download but I just don't here
after that.
Just click on just to start my downloads.
So here you can see the post is starting.
So it will take some time.
Don't have the might as quills which is byte and connector so you can see the process is completed.
So now just go to the.
So here you can see the my Eskil character is downloaded onto dextro.
And now let's start installing the software.
Just click on.
Might as well come this over
this can continue after that again continue agree after that start soccer that just put your system
password
might escalate is start and just copy the good password who come and see this click OK.
Just click Glos.
So now let's go to the second one.
This is my ethical workbench
this drag on application.
It will take some time to install.
So here just click on application so you might as well bench just click on the
click Open
see.
Welcome to my as well workbench which means that all my Eskil about bench is installed successfully.
Just minimize that goes to the last one which is my escalated and dropped by 10.
Just click on zip file.
After that you have a main file here.
Click on this folder and click on the new terminal and follow after that.
Just click by and see if you are using them to be then destroyed by entry.
After that they just set up Doc pre-buy after that.
I installed
so you can see the my Eskil is installed successfully.
No system just closed this terminal.
So here it's all about the installation process.