Welcome to the site and to it you today we are going to learn how to use my as quilt or against the
How To date my ex will come on in Brighton and how to get your data from my screen using Python scripts.
So we had already download our software to get this done on my server.
Just from Systrom could fence my Esquith and start oh my Esquith server.
Just put your system password
so here you can see the server is running now.
Just click when the mice are dead.
Just click on my Esquith workbench.
So here we have my Escuela workbench click on local Steinem's So here you have to put up use a root
password.
So in this we do we are just copied the user password and now I'm going to based here after then just
click OK.
So here you can see the password is expired.
So we have to make another password so just put you on the password after that.
Just put your new password
just click OK.
That put your new password in here again.
Just click OK.
So here we have a debate.
Just click on minimize after that.
Just create your own database by using some commands.
Which is good.
It is a name that it is obvious which is just after the word click.
C'mon.
So here you can see the database created when I click refresh.
So here we have a test date.
I was informed that it was.
We have some table views and some function.
So this is the way to create a database by using my Esquith workbench.
We can clear the same breeder base using my script also.
So here I just opened up my script and now I'm going to implement all my code to connect my Esquith.
So first we have to import a library which is import in secret or connector.
After that you have to make some connection.
So first we have to declare a variable which is C or D and you can write anything on behalf of C M.
Now after that we use this library and my Esquith connector but connect
the the in Texas we have to pass some values which we use to connect our database so the first one is
a user which is what the second one is.
Password
which is
the target one is Horst which is localhost
and the last one is the database.
So if you are working with your current it is then you could declare your database here which is just
in the third line and when I use the cursor which is my cursor so my answer is a variable.
So you can write anything on behalf of my Cosel.
After that I'm going to use the connection which you see will never end.
So this variable.
After that I'm going to write a function which is called a function and in the fourth line I'm going
to execute some code to fetch the data from the database.
So for that we are right
Microsoft Daut execute an sort of.
But in Texas you do Baso short Bebo's which is my Esquith come on and in the last line we have to bring
the database values.
So here I just straight my cursor not fat.
On.
So now let's run this more do
so here.
We did not get any values because our database is empty.
So now let's move to the workbench and not get some tables inside our destiny database.
So for that the first line which is use is come under after that.
And when a did or table cleared Deeble a neighbor table is employed.
Just come on enter here.
Kitzbuhel error which means that we have to add some column inside the table.
So the first one is the ID column after that.
And then after that you have to pass up the key
just put comma and the second is a name and the name is a variable character.
So for that we away.
And after I'd like to prentices and insert the bandages we have to write them in.
These are very.
So this is the way Luke is used to limit this character which means that we can only write the name
from one to three words after that I'm going to use that about the only images or did time for this
day time them Laghi and Velika these all are key words in my Esquith from the last one.
These are human
which is the label collector just working and in the patent this is just past 20.
So here I just
put the command center so you can see the table is created.
We just employ.
So here we can refresh this data.
So inside the database we have an employee table.
Let's move to the script.
So now I'm going again on this Mordieu.
So here we get the result we just employ.
And now I'm going to be at the same table by using Python script.
So here just write the same line just from there.
Come on we can after that just change the name of the table which is student.
Now and this morning you
in the latest gaining strength lifter.
So we have some error here.
So I think there are some indentation error.
So now.
So then just do it again.
So here the process is completed and now it just blows this and goes to my school abutments.
Just click on refresh so you can see the student table is created.
So this is the way to create a table by using my Eskil what went and this is the way to create a table
using Python command that's all about for creating a table using my full workbench and the right hand
commands.