Welcome to them why don't you do it today.
We're going to learn how to insert data in our database by using my Escuela workbench as well as by
tenis script here.
I just opened up my school of workbench and now we use our database which is just after that and hit
enter.
We just come on Enter NOW and when I insert some data by using Insert key word so he destroyed it.
After that going to employed so employees are table in our database.
After that it took pass some paramita.
So the first parameter is the ID.
Second one is only the Tortoni's A B or B.
And the last one is an e-mail.
After that write a values and entered the appendices we have to assign some values.
The first one is ID.
So here I just write one.
So ID is indeed fooled.
The second one has a name field which is a string.
So you just straight elex the turban is also the string.
But it is a date of birth.
So here it is right 1989 0 9 and grindy.
So this is the format to write a did in my A-squared.
After that the last one is a human so you can pass any human
right after the bad analysis and he'd come on to enter.
And here you can see the table is created and one is affected.
And now I'm going to show you how to see the values from the table by writing select Esterbrook Mark
and from employee and hit enter.
Here you can see the names Alex and headed or both and Gannascoli is the e-mail.
So this is the process to insert a data in our database by using might as workbench.
And now let's move to the bitless script insert a data in our database.
So here I just copy all the values we just insert into and after that I'll paste here 10 days.
In addition as I just.
Are Indian correct manner.
So here the values are inserted and now at last I have to write.
SIEGEL And with is variable connection for that period.
And now I'm going to commit these values in our database and now that and just want do sort a view of
the things and venues here.
Name is Peter
the idea as to the date or something like that which is nineteen ninety
and the image is also jeunes hotmail dot com.
So now to save this and this Mordieu.
So here we did not get any error.
So let's move to my school workbench to see whether it is been started or not.
I'm going to clear this one now.
First I have to use a test it is using command enter and the second one is a select start from employees
just click command enter so you can see the second ID is to name the Peter and part 1 is the date of
birth which is 1990 and the last one is that in C there are 12 are gone.
So this is the process to insert a data by using up by a script.
So despite your mice could command regions of mice will code in your eggs a good but entities here and
now I'm going to show you the data.
You know I can script to just do don't come here just write but and microcell
don't fetch on and then just more do so there's some and I'm not there said to fetch I think these are
some I don't.
Because if you write some code which is Microsoft Daut exiguous.
So stay with us.
So Damons and ahu on this Monday.
We got the result which is employer and student and now we're right here which is and it's the Senate
star from the M B and O Y employer.
This will fetch all the data as you see in my school work bench.
We just select the star from employees when we click hit enter.
So there is a pop up.
So all the details here.
Also we just select a star from Employee table and this morning you
we get a result which is the name did second or the name date.
So this is the process to insert data and to show the data by using Pythonesque.