Welcome to the Python tutorial today we are going to learn how to drop a table or we can say how to
keep some values from the table by using my Escuela what went as well as writing a script.
So now let's move to the my ethical work bench.
So here first we have to use the test which is a database.
So here I just would come on enter and now I'm going to see how many values are there in my database.
So here we are selecting store from in LA.
So employees are able to hit enter.
So here we have two values or because of two rows which is elex and Peter and having everyone in two
and now I'm going to lead one to by using our delete key word BP and the delete from name of the table
which is employ after that and straight to we're I will do one.
So here I use equal to one because ideas are unique for all the rows.
So after that hit command enter.
So now when I check whether it is affected or not
from the no employee just click command enter.
So you can see the ID when it is deleted.
Which means that the first row is deleted.
And now let's move to the bitless script to delete the Sikander.
Or you can say delete the second ID.
So just copy some command Drood from employees and most of the vitamines script not just based here.
So no exit good.
So you can see did front employ we are equal to to allow see if this more to do.
And John so here we did not get any error.
So let's move to the my SchoolBook bent to see whether it is affected or not.
And after that he'd come on enter.
So you can see there's a NORDO which means that all the rows are deleted.
So the first is deleted from my Eskil work bench.
And the second row is deleted from the bitless script.
So this is the process to delete the values or we can say delete the rows from database.