Welcome to the I think tutorial today we are going to learn how to send email by using Python script.
So here I just opened up my script and when I create a simple program.
So first we have to import our library which is as I'm typing library.
I seem to be striving for simple made tons of protocol which means that some type is used to send an
email to the mail server and days of pop which is most of his protocol and receivers server which is
used to receive the mail.
So now let's import the some to Libet images and then we'll be able maybe after that get to read the
content.
So he used a radio which is contained You can write anything.
And now here I just wrote Hello I am from witen and now ask could that be used as some debris library
which is maybe equal to Melis a variable you can use anything and simply be maybe Daut capital S.
DP You just simple made Tromso portable and insert the bread into his just I.
I simply thought gmail dot com.
So here we have a free mail server which just some degree that gmail dot com which is from Google.
And now when I say some degree Holstrom which is 5:57 and after that I just write me men don't at all
and put get into this in the next line.
I straight male toward the start
DNS.
So these are the inbuilt method which we used in Python to send any messages displayed or luggin to
lowering the function.
We did use to log into our account.
So here I just put in my e-mail account which is
after that I just put one password and then the next line is to use mail.
Don't send mail.
Put are all on the function which we are used.
So from.
So here we put the e-mail address from.
So it just might.
It does
after the fact that I had that e-mail address to do just
board.
And after that I just put content which is on message and now I just write mail don't close random it
is send.
And now nexted on this Mordieu
or key.
We did docket and it means there the man is saying.
And now let's work with the to Boucek whether it is sent or not.
The sign here by using them 3 3 5 0 3 3 which is what I see what you mean I just put the password.
So here because of the way that it is received or not.
So here you can see the first message or just click on the sender human and the content which is hello
I'm from Brighton.
So this is the way to send any message to any e-mail addresses.