Hi everyone let's get started in this.
You learn about by then try operations.
More specifically opening a file reading from and writing into it closing it and various Father-Mother.
You should be aware of.
So first of all what is a file.
If it is a name location on this still related information it is used to permanently stored data in
a nonvolatile memory like hard disk.
Since the random access memory is well let's say which loses its data when compared to the stone tool.
We use flyer's for future use of the data.
So when we want to read from or write to a file we need to open it first when we are done.
It needs to be closed so that the resources that are tied to the file are treat.
Hence in Python the file operations takes place in the following order.
First one opening fire second one both forming operations like reading or writing up ending exit.
The third one closing your file.
So let's do have a look at the first one opening your file by that has a built in function called open
to open a file.
This function will return a File object also called a handle as it is used to read all modify the file
accordingly.
In this first case we just bought the name of the file.
This will be XTi as a string to the function open and to do so we should be in the same directory.
Would the desktop be the results.
And in the second case we specified before Bob do read me don't be XTi in this case we needn't be in
the same directory I read Middleby XTi it is x then we can specify the.
While opening the file also in more we specify whether we want to read or write or up into 5.
We also specify if we want to open the file in the text mode or in binary mode.
So let's have a look at the Motz.
These are the mods that are supported by Python.
It is for reading and reading in text mode is the default mode here.
And this more we get strings when reading from the file on the other hand in the binary mode.
The more return bytes.
And this is the more to be used when dealing with non-fixed files like images.
So W stands for writing and this will create a new file if the mentioned file does not exist or it will
drag in the file.
If the name exist then extenso exclusive creation.
If the file already exist the operation fees and A-stan for opening file for upbuilding at the end of
the file with a drunk getting it.
And this also will create a new file.
If the name does not exist and B is the default text mode and be sensible the binary more than we are
dealing with.
You may just or really all we have used these binary more and this blessed line is used for combining
more than one.
More like reading and writing or writing in binary like that.
Then I like all other languages.
The character here does not imply the number 97 undelete is encoded using ASCII or other valid encodings.
Moreover the default encoding is platform dependent.
In Windows it is C.P 4:59 do but in Linux it is you ate like this.
So you must not also relay on the default encoding.
Or else our guard will behave differently in different platforms.
Hence when walking Why isn't there more.
It is highly recommended.
You specify the encoding type like this.
Since we are using Linux we are using the encoding babe.
You'll be a great hand here.
We just opened the file in read mode within gaurdian.
It would be a feat so just to have a look at other examples.
Also in the first case we just open the door still be XTi in the default mode.
With this ruling in ex-MIL and the second case we supplied the value so that we can write indexable.
And third guess we are opening an MH goal MH to B and B in really last minute.
So when we are done with the operations to the file we need to properly close closing the file.
Three of the resources that were tied with the file.
I had this done using the close of the like here even though it has a garbage collector to clean up
the referenced objects.
But we must not relay on it to close the file.
So here we just open the doors will be XTi in the default mode with encoding you defeat and we will
both form some file operations here and after that we have to close it by calling if not close then
this mother is not entirely safe if an exception of course.
When we are both forming some file operations with the file then the exists without closing the file.
So a safer way is to use the try finally block in try.
We are trying to open this to be XTi within coding be feet and we will perform some operations here.
And finally we are closing it by calling after close.
So this murder.
We are glad indeed that the file is properly closed the event and exception of course here causing the
program to load to stop.
The best way to do this is using big statement like here.
This ensures that the file is closed when the block inside this statement is exited.
We don't need to explicitly call the close mother since it is done internally.
So I strongly recommend you use with open
like he'll to do the operations with sites.
So that's all for now.
All the operations are related to fire.
Like reading from file spending to read writing do it will be handled in the upcoming reviews.
So keep watching.
Thank you.