Welcome to them why can't you do it.
Today we are going to loan file handling in Boston which means that how to create file using Python
script and how to make some data in text file using byte in the script.
So now let's move to the first topic which is how to create a text file using brighteners script.
So here I just open up writing a script.
So here just click file click new file.
And here we have a new script just to save this script in dextro
or named Regis file.
Don't be like So here you can see there is a script which is file that we like.
And now I'm going to create a text file using my script to just write a variable which is fine.
You can give any name to this variable after that.
Just write a function which is open and inside the open function.
If you pass some emitter so the first emitter is the name of the file which is right and the extreme.
You can give any name to this file.
And after that you have to put a format of the file with this text file.
And after the parameter just put a comma after the comma we put a mod.
So there are four or five modes.
So the first mode is a real mode which is used to read the file.
Second what is the right man would you use to write the file.
And the third one is the Brennaman.
So apparently used to Edita you know existing file.
So here I'm going to use the right word to create a text file.
So I just put w after the W.
I have to put a plus sign to this blessing in disguise that if there is a file in a pod.
So just use those file to write something.
And if there is no file in the part then just create a file.
Each name is white and or text.
So here I'm going to use are the bluebloods.
If you move this plus sign so this the blue means you want to use a file which is already exist in the
box.
And after that you want to write something in the file.
So now you put plus here and now let's run this Mordieu thing is it's index error.
Sawston
So here we did not get any error just move to the next door to here you can see the text file whose
name is byte under the XP and into the text file.
There's no data.
So this is the process to create a file using brightener script.