In this world you're going to learn how to do better instead of fine.
But you can say how to create our data into the existing files.
So we had already created a file which is right under the XTi and now I'm going to use up right in the
script which is fine or B-Boy from Dexter.
Just click on file.
Just click on open click on desktop and click on finder.
Be right.
So here I am when I use debut we get used to what I define.
And now I'm going create a string.
Well just last year after that and would assign some interesting pitches.
Hello world.
So here the hello world is a string which is stored in the variable Astier.
And now I'm going to use a function which is quite fine.
Right.
Instead the president says I'm going to use a variable which is Astier this hello world is a store inside
this function.
Right after the fight to close this file using Glos function.
And now let's run this model.
So here we did not get any error.
So let's move to the file which is 560.
Just open it.
So here you can see the string which is hello world.
So this is the way to get all data in your file using bytes and script.
And now I'm going to do this data received this and just close this
inaugurates will do that by conscript and here I'm going to change something which is still your input.
And so in good story duchies and some data
or non-Arabs from this Mordieu.
Now I'm going to write some to choose from
by to just click do no search for the files just by you can read.
And here you can see de-listing which is I'm from Brighton which we had typed you know Batan script.
So this is the way to create a data using by Pennis script.