In this video we are going to learn how to open data in our existing files.
So while we use append instead of right when we use the Mukhlas or we can say w for writing the data
then the existent would have been deleted.
Then we create a new data but then we use the mode then the new data is added after the existing data.
So here we already have something you know quite extreme which is I'm from bison and I'm going to append
some data using email which is and now just and just to see does more do or more new here.
I'm going to search something with just chrome Indio.
Just click onto my Kirchner to get the text for just right under DXi.
Here you can see there is another.
Did I just.
I'm from India which is rendered after the existing data which is I'm from python.
And now when me use w here
just to run this morning you are going wrote something.
Hello world.
Just clicked into the file which is why it's under 60
so you can see a new do they generated and exit Sundari deleted.
That's why we don't use w I think some data we always use our print.
I do indeed because deathblow will delete the existing data and it will create a new reader but when
we use append mode then the new the devil added after the existing data.
So this is the way to add some data on the now file using byte script.