Welcome to buy them to do today we are going to talk about numbers in Brighton.
Now my is in big debt I live in Brighton which is used to store a numeric value which means that number
always used to store up in desirable not to string values.
So this is all about numbers in Python.
Now let us understand through a simple example.
Here I will bring up my pencil and now I'm going is a good example of number how you can say I assigned
a numeric value in a variable.
Now do this again isn't it.
Which means that the variable is stored the numeric value.
So this is the example of numbers.
And now as we know that by support for different numeric type which is indeed a long integer flawed
and complex.
So you already know in the long and bitter.
I'm going to explain you flawed and complex.
Now for float equal to seventeen point six.
This is a float.
Welcome to Q&amp;A.
Having good results and in 1:06 which means that they're very well Istana.
Well Lou now for complex values equal to the helpless 45 which means that really the deal part and a
45 is a million.
But again my goodness we get our complex Velu which means that you'd automatically store the new value
which is a complex value.
So it is all about to buy 10.
Now I'm going to spin you some method which is used in numbers.
Now the first method is absolute method which is s method.
Now for that simply that is a good absolute method.
When I get a variable and giving them a loan minus Well it is a negative value.
Now when I bring this value with absolute method to ABS and to help me get the absolute 12 it is a positive
in the value.
So these is all about the absolute value.
The next method is the sealing method which is denoted by c i l this function are not accessible directly.
So we need to import more Mondial called a method model.
Initially I'm going to import a model which isn't Mathman do.
Now I'm going to execute a program.
After that I'll explain you what is the scene method.
So now initially giving of a little.
One two three.
And now I'm going to print is Velu using Mathman do it.
I call her my model.
So here we get the result Hardeen which means that Silma thirds are always stored the smallest and zero
value which is good at that.
And then the reference reference will do.
So it is the smallest and is a value greater than the reference value.
I think today is the smallest and is of value after the twelve point three to three.
It will not give you the floor well it will always give you the invisible or we can say that C are used
to start the next value.
So whatever else you have you get.
You had given Google Print 2 4 2 3 9 8.
Anything it would simply give you the next in.
So this is that Hardeen in the next indiscernible.
So now this is all about the cell method.
The next 23rd is the floor my third floor My third is just similar to the Silma third.
So initially we have to import our model Matt
here.
I'm going to execute a program.
After that I'll explain you
equal to twelve point two three and now I'm going to call this my third.
So here we get the results.
Well so which means third floor are used to that the largest in deserve no less than the reference vendor.
So which is the largest and is of value is not greater than this reference value.
So I think well is the largest And is it a venue or we considered flawed.
Are used to get our previous in these Ravello as the reference value.
So the previous indiscernible knew then the reference values the Gwen.
So if you put padding point three four fourteen point four we will get the previous interior below which
is 13 or 14.
So these are all about the floor method.
The next method is exponential method exponential method is just similar to the math exponential method.
So these methods are not accessible directly.
So we need to import my math model
here.
I boarded a math model and now I'm going to simply print our exponential value of two.
So here we get the result.
Seven point thirty eight.
So this is all about the exponential method.
The next method is a maximum of 10 denoted by a x.
So for that we don't need to import a math model.
We can access directly so equal to max
45 and 2.
Parent of a new.
So here we get the desired 45.
So 45 is the maximum in this list of item.
So this all about the Maxima entered.
The next method is the min method and be considered a minimum method for that equal to m i n.
Right.
And Jim you were in the same variable
I mean print.
Really.
So here we get the minimum value which is too.
So it is all about the minimum method.
The next method is the power method the power method.
It is similar to the mathematics method which means there are two to the poultry two to about four.
What they were really good about it was simply give the lizard for that and would simply exit the bar
method.
So first we have to import a math model because these methods are not accessible directly.
Now I'm going to print Velu B or W and now two former three hit trees the power of this it offends Velu
so any heavy get the result.
Which means that dude with about three is eight which is due to the power three is it.
So these is all about the power method.
The next time a third is A-squared mentored A-squared method it does similar to the Met A-squared.
So for that we have to first import Ahmadullah Matt and now I'm actually going to print spreaded real
math Dorte Eskew.
Hundred.
So we get the deserts and this kind of squared up hundred is simpler then.
So there's almost a square root method.
The next method is a mod method.
More death method is used to get in zero value apart under floatable really do our part which means
that you'll get the sceptered value of that and the float.
So now fussily and we import Ahmadullah meant and now England execute the program.
After that explain you
mean f and giving of a lapel pin 9 0.
So we get that Izard here.
This is a flawed part of this reference Lewton which is gulper 9:0 and this is a robot which is a.
So what math more deft does it will separate the Indie's revenue and the floor.
Well Lou in different parts.
So this is all about the mod f method the last method is the logger method not method really don't need
to logarithmic Melu are the best value.
So for that we have to import a model.
And I'm going to simply execute our lock and value we'll do metadata log and hit plan.
And the base is also 10.
And is the base.
So here we get the result 1.
So we know that locked down is the one that is all about number in Brighton.