Welcome to the By tend to do it here.
Today we are going to talk about acception in Python.
An exception is event which occur during the execution of the program.
Or we can say an exception is the adder which can be handled by the program.
The exception which are already available in the Python are called the built in exception.
One more thing don't confuse between the error and the exception because edit and exceptions are not
the same.
Suppose if the program again gets an error in the program and he can do something to emulate the error
then it is called an exception.
If the programmer cannot do anything in case of error then it is called an error not an exception.
A programmer can create his own exception code use a pain exception.
Now let's move to the example where we can see how exception.
Ago.
So first let's understand about the syntax error and how it is different from exception because sometime
be confused between syntax error and the exception errors.
So let's move to the examples here.
I open a Python script and after that and agreed to fi's one for syntax error and the second for exception.
So first I'm going to get a program where we can see what is a syntax error.
So first I simply dig in both
some values.
So here we can see this is the input which is stored in the variable x.
So after that I'll simply break the values of x here we we've done this Mordieu and you can see we get
a result to give some values.
But then they get the result.
So what is a syntax error in this program.
When I can but do I.
And B you all d.
Then here we can see we get a syntax error in this program.
So this is a syntax error.
And now I'm going to tell you what is the exception.
So first I'm going to again dig in Buddh
And doesn't this and this input is indeed a type.
And after that I'll simply print off X so this in user input is stored in this ex-buddy and this expeditor
will printed out not this do you can see the program is correctly done after that and simply put in
3.
Then we get one day.
It is old now.
I wonder this program again is going to simply type hello which is a string.
We get a value error so these errors are exception error which means that these errors can be handled
by a programmer.
So this is the difference between syntax error and exception error syntax error can't handle by a programmer
but the exception can be handled by the programmer.