In this studio I'm going to teach you how to handle the exception.
So why we need to handle the exception because the purpose of handling the acceptance is to make the
program robust robust means a strong robust program does not terminate in the middle.
So now let's move to the examples before going to like some example we need to know what the steps followed
to handle the exception.
So the first step is try block by block means then there may be a possibility of exception in the program
the programmer will put all the code in the try block.
The second step is except block the program.
Right.
Except block where he should misplay the exception to do.
Or a custom message that the.
Finally finally block is hidden in the master.
And finally block I use to execute the program vendor the exception or not.
So now let's move to that example to understand the exception handling here.
I just opened up items and now I'm going to create a simple program to show you how to handle the exception.
So now as I already said the quarter should we keep inside the block.
So I simply wanted to print something
and write something.
And after that they just said the second step is to accept
it will burn some messes.
If the code is incorrect inside the block
I need some Going to the
here and now.
And where is my due.
So here I'm going to simply write something with.
Hello world here.
We did not get any error.
And now I'm going to get something inside this used of move this character insert the input matter.
This input my part is incorrect.
And now I'm I this more do.
So here to get up except Messers please write something correctly.
We did not get any error message because the excerpt will simply show you the user defined message.
And when I simply print this money again we get the exact lizard which is.
So this is a block and this is the except block and now I'm going to create a simple example to understand
the exception handling more.
And now I'm using my loop after that and I put two and in the loop when I declare I blog.
And except look inside the table.
It will take some input.
We do which is in brute
then after that it will break the block.
If the input is correct
and that except block that I'd clue.
So now I'm going to do this in boot.
So here it's very well except for indecent.
Well you know I'm one of them this morning to say the program is executed correctly and I'm glad I did
something did.
So it would accept in Deezer.
And now let's do it again hello.
You can see please write correctly this except block will.
So a message please write correctly.
After that if again something is true.
We get the message.
Please.
Correctly so until it will get busier that it will persist.
So this is the absolute example to understand the block and accept Block.
And now we are going to use a finally block in this program
to simply being a massive do over.
Which means that this final blog will not depend on this excerpt and this type blog
whenever we type in December.
You can see the live blog is executed.
And now if you have some different venue which is Astrue so you can see this either accept the message.
And this is the final message.
So here we can see the final message will not depend on this excerpt and this blog.
If your dialogue is right or wrong this time statement of in print at the end.
So this is not optional.
Instead the exception so if you want to print something and the last.
Then we use the find the live blog.
Or if you want to exclude something in the last.
Then we have to use the final block.
So this is about our exception in Python.