Welcome to the white and do even today we're going to talk about live in by then the list is in which
you do that I mean by time which I used to store our list of item list is created using a square to
record and each item placed inside the list with separate coalmines.
I don't insert the list have their own index relative.
That means that each item in the list had their own position which is denoted by.
So these are new.
Now let us understand to a simple example of list.
I open up my pencil and now I'm going to with some simple example of Mr..
So initially I created it very well.
And that's I think the list I see that list is created using is quite a bit good.
So the emptiness because we don't have any item inside this list.
So now I'm going to assign some item in this list to the first I don't use a string.
The second I don't use a can do that right.
You thought I don't know it's true but something does have a new.
Which is the alphanumeric menu.
So I'm going to print this list to.
So here we get the result of this list which isn't good.
It's you can do that there the many Benue.
But this is all about this in my turn.
Next I'm going to explain to you how to access the menu then send the list how to observe the list and
how to delete the list.