So now I'm going to access the item from the list.
So here I collected the list assigning some item.
The first item is a mystery.
The second item is a fraud.
Well you hair.
I'm with the actors the I don't know having the expedition 0.
So for that you have to give the index when you show the head of the disorder and get the result by
10 which is a string.
So these are all about the accessing the value from the list.
So another second think is that how to update the list updating the list means that we have to change
the item we have of did this item.
So initially we didn't want to come in said the list.
And the second item is flawed will you.
So now I'm going to change this floor will look with some industry so for that I'm going to using our
next a new one and assigning a string to her hello and now I'm going to print this whole Jane.
So here we get the result we have to item the first item in this tree.
And the second item is the updated string.
So initially we have floatable Lou.
And after that we have a string with which is hello could is all about updating the list.
So the next thing is how to delete the list deleting the list and how to move the list.
So for that we have to use a method D.
And now I'm again using the expedition's of one.
So I'm going to lead this item into question 1 and after that I'm going to print the list so here we
get the result.
So how do we get there isn't only one item.
Because the second item is deleted using the b l method.
So this is all about the accessing deleting and updating the list.