That next My third is in sort my third inserted my third is just similar to the comprendo my third.
But the main difference is that he inserted the inserted my third we can give her an expedition of the
I don't what we can say there where we want to add the item inside the existing list.
So now I'm going to create a list which is the same list.
So here we have some item in the list.
And now I'm going to insert some item here.
So it i then the odd insert.
For now I need to put the index value so the inexpensive too.
I want to add some item.
So here.
Hello.
And now I'm going to print the updated Velu which is the heavy get that reason the updated.
Harry can see.
Hello he said.
Inexpertly shut up.
Through and that the three is shifted to the next mission of three.
So this all about start my third.