The last third is sort of my third sort my third of it simply sort of the item from the list which means
that begins on the idea of either increasing or decreasing order.
Now I'm going to start the item.
So here I created a list.
Now I'm going to simply sort this list.
Now I'm going to print the updated list with the.
So here we get the result which is in increasing order which means that the first item is the lowest
I don't and the last I don't is the highest I don't have the larger value.
So if you want to get the value in decreasing order then it means simply that he was the sorting items
on each week.
This was trying to help me get the result in negating order.
So here we have two example.
This is in increasing order and this is in decreasing order of starting.