Heidrun now that Stu and ASEAN and which will make use of the file murders and operations and all.
So what I'm going to do is I have to create X-File A B C then another player for Apple for banana Fortuny
and at last I just want to go and get any old Joy in both these X Files and to make a new file then
do the split.
That is my modem.
So in order to do that I just want to make the don't X Files for first.
So for that I would use the mother again just come and.
Don't we all.
I just named all the file as a TO SEE see the XTi.
And that is in the right not at the end as F 1.
And here we.
And the other file opening also by just adding a call here and open
floats.
Don't be XTi
in the right Modigliani and at the end as
then Andoe.
And just to add some big data to the water supply it's.
So first learn if one thought right.
The then just call me this and raised it for five days.
So most six days I took it.
Then one door but I be Flunder right I see then if doodled right.
For both
you like
for
banana slash in your line and for
Chevy
slash and
let's get started on this line over here and don't make this one too.
And also add new lines to these lines also.
Just silly.
And let's go to the terminal.
And it
playpen.
And in order to see this we need not to be always open the file using the command prompt.
We can also open the files of it to see and thoughts are results residing.
So let's see if we have ABC and then through the XTi we have for Apple for banana for sure.
So when it snows it and go to the court again
then we have done this.
So let's come out and in order to all get this we have to use
buy in board.
I so it's so important for us from those in both
eyes it said.
And now let's open the fire.
Would just call the food or leave something else like that and just don't get any of the fires.
We are saved.
And let's see what happens.
So we open
all this they said it bought the XP
and I will open this in right.
And as
it has again been Karma I have to open the other two was also that this was nice.
You see the XTi and I'm opening it in the default mode.
Since I don't have to write anything into that I just want to read that and the other one open
fire fruit's the XTi
ass f I just forgot to add if one here
as one.
And after that I just want to you do this.
For that I am using for
four.
This is the all
no let's index Ofex but I just want to get to rid of that since I didn't want that right now for
Line 1 for my line do
see
in basis I just want to boss this F1 and F2 since we are opening it as opening a Boosey as if Wonderfalls
S S2.
So if one or more if two last goaland and then we want you all can get it for that.
That's right.
We just start adding space for both of them so that we have a format like this.
And after that
Dauth format your format like that format and in basis the half line one
group
this is a function.
And also all my lines do all off-Strip.
So we have our family or the now let's see what happens when it get run.
So just go with the terminal and run this again.
And now let's go to the files and we have this rest of the XTi and just open it.
Yeah we got a foot apple before banana and seafood chili.
That's it.
That's how we could get a fire under fire and make a new one.
And where the fires are not affected by doing so they are asked like before.
So that's all the boat can get to needing a fire.
Oh.
So that's all for now.
Keep watching.
Thank you.