Hi everyone let's get started in the last two Duryea we have done and agreement I mean that we have
used some built in functions like isip and Ostap here.
So you might be wondering or is the focus of all these functions here.
So let's do have a look at each one of them deeply.
So let's start with the C functions here and in order to use all these functions we have to import that
isip from you to do things like here and the function returns.
I list two books were I to on.
The element from each of the argument sequences or it delivers like if one understood here and that
is done listee strangulated in length of the length of show argument sequence and when there are multiple
arguments which are all of the same length.
This function is similar to the map function with any argument of note and with a single Siku an argument
it will return a list of one tuple and with no argument it will return an empty list.
So keep that in mind.
And those on the left to right evaluation order of the boots get guaranteed.
So let's have a look at another example.
Here we have this x and y having same length and we have C with the C function here like this.
This is its index and equal to done first value of false list called My First values second list Colma
second value first list.
My second rule of second is.
And so on and the set in conjunction with this Tottle Braider like here can be used to and simple list
like the second line.
The second last line like Q and this book are doing to
and no let's do half look good the ice function.
The ice function will make an iterator that aggregates elements from each of the if that is like C except
that it returns and it do.
Instead of list
so the left to right evaluation order of the delivers is guaranteed in this fall.
So let's have a look at the example here.
In this we have a do list.
One two three and a b c here.
And we are using this ice function here and we are bringing the I then we'll print it like this.
Here you can see
here we have not having the square brackets.
Like in this so that's the difference.
And it is not separated by mom.
Also like
and we have another one which is the largest
difference of ice and isip largest.
If we are using isip then the ABC and Ex-White will be isip like a x and B Y like this and in the case
of iSuppli just it will be like a b c d e x y and we can also supply a food value like minus here and
this will be giving us a x y z.
Right.
See this isip and the fill value is combined with the C and D like C dash and B the like this.
So if we are
using it then we will not get the C dash dash like here.
And we want to play it through value like here.
So that's all about I see and I see just now we have another one.
The Ostap and the murdered Ostap burns a copy of the string in which all gas has been stripped from
the end of the string like a default whitespace characters.
So it's you have Fosdick's and we're here we have a species.
And before as and after this as we have lot of spaces and after this since we are using Ostap the it
will strip the right side of S and we get species like here and easier being a like this then we will
get the B D and this is a good strip.
And if we are having a B B then it will strip both a B and B and we will get an empty string like this.
And in the case of this b c a b b b.
If you are slipping a B this food strip this a B and B and B will get ABC on.
And we also have Elsje in order stood out from the left side.
And if we want to strip some special things in between.
So we have.
So we can use also.
So that's all about strip strip and Strip.
So keep watching.
Thank you.