First of four wheel drive alone learn Dometic overtake us.
So what are the operators and the medical operators are used to both from domestic operations like addition
subtraction multiplication division modulus Xplornet.
So let's begin to integrate anti-GPL from some examples.
Let's open them to bigger
worked like that.
All right.
So we are going to repeat or not.
So instead of this python interpreter Let's enter to interact by the interpreter.
So our indirect indirectly by the interpreter and interpreter are seen by indirect do in the middle
is nothing but a normal bike that in the corridor with Stylites on it.
I mean it has the various new functionalities and attributes except rest of the user base for a minute.
So let's end when do interactive by an interpreter.
Basically for non-bird don't really really build realtime just by them.
But in a body in case of fire indirect to individuals we need to use AI AI before it might work.
So this is nothing but interactive fiction.
All right so we are into or biting into a bit and let us know what the operators are trying to declared
to values with some are by assigning values to it.
I mean I could get two variables by assigning some ballastic
equal nine
Beag equal to yet both from
Asian point
B.
So that's.
That's imply that apart from Elisha and in Dubai too when we are using just the word print in order
to bring the value of a variable.
But in case of bidon to point Armon byte entry we need to use this statement as a function.
I mean Bing has been converted into function by the Dupont's like roundoff Glaspie.
When God bless b c so you've been able to print the value of a variable and do this by using print as
a statement and print as a function.
All right.
So let's also know let's move on some.
Ms.
Substraction
sorry.
B.
That's it.
Nine minutes is equal to one and as a multiplication.
Let's take some of them.
I mean values by creating some different variants
in Python.
You can buffer multiplication by using an operator stack.
So this was awkward.
Now
let's get to this division
what so are many.
When we divided the divide into Yea by B I mean 4 by 3 million the value is 1.
And the next one was Margulis.
So Words mean more to us madrassas is nothing but a reminder of the division operation.
For example the Colt 45 Yeezy called Six.
And when you type in modulus B.
So the output should be three.
So we got down to the street when we divided 45 by 6 we mean the actual question was 6 sevens 42 and
the remainder was three.
So that was their actual output.
If you don't understand that I show you.
Six forty five.
So so in Division of General mathematics if you divide it 45 by six I mean the value should be 7 6 7
42.
And that reminder should be easy.
So this was an actual non-idiots you
know exponent.
So what is in my experience exponent is nothing but extra for a.
Let's also try to give an example for this.
Let's take easy calls for an easy called 3.
So I can cite for that.
Easy for me is equal to three.
So how you implement the exponent functionality in PI that simple did that was that B why we declared
B's call for B must be 3 OK whatever.
44 or 4 is nothing but Duvel 6.
So this is equal to fall into four into four four.
So this was the actual processing behind the exponent functionality.