Lead and turn into combative you know because.
So what I combatted you know this comparison operators are used to compare the values on both sides
of it.
They are also less relational operators.
So some of the combat.
I mean the come down Bajan operators are greater than Lizanne does not equal to less than or equal to
equal to not equal to and not equal to going out of business and can also build in the dungeon symbol
monocoque.
Let's see an example for this.
Easy code 9 to be easy could create looks initially first check and credit that vector is greater than
should be true of course 9 is going to end yet.
And also Giclas that is less than be false of course is greater than I mean B and less than 9 and hence
is false.
Now let's say that equal to it is better than or equal to
B.
I'm sorry.
We should we should but we shouldn't give any space between those operators.
Yes.
Listen Michael to me.
Of course it is false.
And we're losing money on it.
Equal to whether one is equal eight.
Was that true.
Let's go
to please.
Azo here.
If you single people do then we are then it indicates that we are assigning a value to anybody.
But if you use double equal do it means that we are checking the value of both variables here.
OK so next.
Not equal to the is not equal to the two of course it is true.
Nine is not equal galiot and not equal to has two symbols.
I mean this one and and another one.
Let's also check with that.
Yes of course it's true.