So well what I sent into orbit is actually assignment operators saw use it to assign land use to variables
and the different types of assignment values are in the world.
Let's see what minus equals.
And so on until the one because in the past.
OK.
OK let's try these examples.
5.
So we have assigned a variable.
I mean we are assigned a value or find a variable.
You don't get reading variable you and assign a value to.
So these are all the more assigned values.
Now let's check what is meant by place equal to nothing but it adds the right side value to the left
side value and its end result will be the left side right.
OK let's see an example.
Yea plus equal to 2.
So the result will be 7.
That's pretty.
So hold the pipe help right in a calculator that yea less equal to 2.
Yes insanity was to using that again because to take one to endless two.
So this was.
So this statement was actually called A's goal is to luck in short.
By then I'll be able to modify Python in this manner.
Let's take that easy call to center is equal to bless to your best to win it.
So.
So this was an book.
So this is all about equal.
And similarly with minus equal if he is equal to four
a minus equal to 1.
So this is equal to easy called eight minus one seems easy call for is equal to four minus 1 which is
nothing but 3:28 that's all.
And that's all with the multiplication and of the division.
I'll If you want example let's take an example and equality for each division equal to two Donta should
be two.
Which is nothing but full by two is nothing but a by two.
And he would
next be easy called Musical 3
according to.
So he agreed to do it because it's been beat.
OK.
And now the modulus more as we have discussed just now the more or less is nothing but a reminder of
the division operation.
OK let's initialize another bailable call see is equal to
level see modulars see more or less equal to two Donalson began.
I mean if you divide by two the are the minder was one actually plug in C.
So they might be one.
OK.
Now the last one was exponential
less easily available.
Is equality.
And let's try to take the bar of 4 which is now which is nothing by 80 were
equal to 4 3 in the.
Yes that's right.
OK.
Now we have got one assignment up us.
Let's dig into our big ways operators.