So what a big place oblateness big boys operate as compass values in binary formats.
These operators walk on in distance when performing big boys are and in DS as initially these Indians
and ready to buy in any form and then some of them Batjer.
All right.
So let's begin to pick some examples.
And the big leagues operators are.
And this Simmo was all as binary and binary art and binary Zot X or binary compliment.
This is nothing but the negation and binary shift and binary shift
lips.
Let's get to know first about this binary and
let's try to create two variables over here is it.
90 is equal to 18 so be initialized and we created two variables with values 19 and 18.
Let's call for advice and operators on these two variables.
And B.
So the output was 80.
How.
So in the bag on BIDEN First can we do this 19 engaging Dubai in any form.
And then performs and operation.
Let's check what is a binary format of 19.
How is been able to take that in byte and simple.
We have some function.
So the binary format of YIG which isn't which is nothing but 19 is 1 0 1 1.
Let's also know the binary format of
the binary form of B.
OK.
Biden compares these to binary formats over here and finds the result in binary divorcement and then
it can What's that binary format into India.
OK so how we can be is actually how we both homes and Operation Biddy's binary format.
OK.
In case of an resultant value will be 1 if bought 0 values or 1.
Ok let's try to understand understand this with an example.
Let's copy this.
So of byte on both forms the and Operation result in value of 1 and 0.
I mean the result in comparison of two digits will be 1 if bought our visits are 1 in guess of an operation.
For example here 1 and 0 1 and 0 should be 0.
We've gone from start 1 and 1 is 1 and 0 0 0 0 1 and 0.
So I think it was one action.
So the resultant value should be one only if bought combatted in values are what otherwise the value
should be zero.
For example the board values are what he had the book conversion values he had that one and hence the
resulting value was 1 in guess of.
And similarly with 1 and 1 is 1 and 1 and 0 since.
Would that not once and one is one value 1 and 1 is that is all the result in that it should be zero.
So and So initially pikemen got the result by comparing two binary formants of two in these as as this
one.
So let's try to find out what was indeed notation of these binary form it's all you can able to find
in the format of a binary does it's by using a function called in Python.
Been off this one
so it's not been actually Binny's use it to come more to the Indies as in binary formats.
If you want to convert the binary pharmaco end in disaster.
So you need to use it if until God in desire.
Indeed indeed.
All right.
So this is a value of 18 actually
arrive.
So this is the value of Ailey.
Actually this is similar with our operation in case I forget of course we are.
I mean we got to know about an operation and now let us know about this operation so how Python compares
to binary formats.
I mean do numbers actually.
So for 1998 in these two are the binary formats and byte and initially compares the binary formats and.
And the result will be a binary and this binary will become region doing this at.
So now we got bored and.
And let us know what our in case of binary are the result and I mean the result will be one if it is
to one of the bits is 1.
For example previously the result will be 1.
Only if both values are 1 but in the case of are the result will be the result will be 1.
If at least one of these conversion Well this was one.
OK.
And now the output will be 1 seems at least one of the two.
What else is one the value will be 1 0 since no all values 1 1 0 1 and it just seems at least one of
the two converging values is one the value will be 1.
So this is a value of art as and now Python can load this binary format to it.
So let's check what's so what was the value of it.
And our sorry.
So the value should be of us here
all right so this was all about
binary OR.
And what was and what this binary export binary.
OK.
More in case of binary X or the result will be one.
If it leads to 1 which is one button but not both will be 1.
I mean when when comparing these two values at least one of the values should be what if both the value
should be 1 the value should be zero and and essentially busy.
So this is a condition in exo.
OK let's deal with it since at least I mean if both should be one the value should be 0 0 0 0 if both
are 1.
The value should be zero if at least one that should do one.
I mean if a list one values one the resultant value should be 1.
So this is a binary format in Python by the to end this as 1928 and so what is indeed a representative
representation of this.
B is well OK.
Let's check off what.
OK so the binary format of 1 was this one.
So so now we got to know about binary binary or similarly binary complement in guess on binary content.
When you initialize and then with easy called 9.
So how you would negate a value is it is nothing but you.
So the negation of nine is nothing but 8.
And you can also convert this minus 10 to 9 by using and then negation like mightest in negation back
to nine.
So this is all about.
By then complement or by the negation.
So what is left.
No we learn about left
left is nothing but the left value is moved by Nemeroff bits left.
I mean inspired by like I mean the left values more left by the Nemeroff bit specified by like value
for example let's take the gold and see what is a binary binary form of it.
It's nothing but a double one double zero and one double zero.
When we apply live shift operators I mean shift operation on this variable.
Yea let's check what was the result of this
too.
So what is a binary for.
So the resultant Indesign was what.
Let's take the band in the format of this form that
so you can able to see that.
Now WWE the one double double one was the one that was it a saw or the value the binary format has moved
to its left to reflect back into its right so.
So it has more left actually.
Now let's take a ball right
next to initialize and available.
Right.
Let's and right shift operation on these very
too.
Was that really when you say OK let's take it.
So initially we need to check what was a binary representation of B
B.
Ok so the binary presentation of bit was double and was it a wonder.
Let's check and see how I played the blame the right shift operation on this variable be.
So the reason that the result was 25.
So let's say that by an 80 percent it's not 25.
And and and see where that goes by 80 percent in and has been moved Booby's it's right or not
would be fine.
Yes.
So double one double 0 1 these binary digits has me has more Booby's it's right by the leading 0 0 0.
We've been able to see the length of this one two three four five six seven and here and here the left
was only five.
That means he has more to do this right.