In this video I'm going to explain some function which I used in Japan the first My third is lenth my
third.
This method will get the number man inserter especially when you consider it would give you the list
of items which exist in the handbook.
So we had to pick some example.
So I did a couple assigning some I don't.
Now I'm going to read to the left on this topic.
So here I am using Beldi and the third and I put a
right and there's more to
it isn't it.
Because we have it.
I don't intend this.
So it is all about the length the next time my code is Max my third Max method don't you.
The element will have the max number that we have to create or double.
So here I it a couple I see some item and now I'm going to print some new way I use max method.
Hey I think it's going to do
heavy good.
The reason for the pain because in this double the I don't fuku bit I have done this badly.
So these is all about the max my target.
So then next my third minute third minute third just similar to the max method but it will simply be
done.
The minimum value from the top for that.
Could I use my method.
Am I.
And had I done this more do Brigade-Major 34 because petfood is just consider this double is all about
the min my current the last my third is how to convert the copper to the next.
Or you can say how to convert the list into equal.
So first we're going to convert the items to list data.
So here I created a double.
We have some item in and this double.
Now I'm going to go into the list.
They get them it will be.
And now I want to use list here.
I will say that is this variable pay it either double.
No I'm going to simply create the variable b k bigger an so here we see the items are enclosed in quite
a big card which means that these are the list item.
And now we can order item from list to open.
So first we have to create a list.
Here we have some item in the list.
And now I'm going to convert into the number I used.
I and that that it wouldn't be.
And now I'm going to use my third You B and B and I put in.
Which is a mistake.
Now I'm going to simply print it with B.
Harrigan these are the all items I enclosed within a band and this is.
Which means that these items are double items.
This is all about the double in white.