Welcome to the 500 we're here today we are going to learn the concept of hoops in Python.
So what is the full from of boops with the object oriented programming and system.
So the entire concept is derived from the word we just classes and objects.
So what is a class and what is the object.
A class is a model which consists of matter and data an object is anything that really exists in the
world.
So let's take a simple example to understand the process and the objects.
Suppose there is a building inside the city so the building exists physically inside the world.
So the building is the object.
And now suppose you have a paper instead of paper.
There is a sketch of the building.
So the paper is a blueprint of that building.
So the paper is called the classes which means that the people considered all the models which is data
and method to build a building.
So this is the class of people and there is the object which is physically exist inside the world.
So now let's take another example to understand the class as an object.
So here we have two things in Lampron side we have a recipe to bake a cake.
And in the left hand side we have some cakes.
So as we know that a recipe is needed to bake a cake.
So this recipe is called a class and the gate is called the object.
So the main difference between the class and object here which is a kitchen but you can bet it is big.
It means that we actually exist in the world but we can't eat up a recipe.
So when we bake a cake which means that we create an object according to the class definition plus definition
means that ingredient and the method which exist in the recipe.
So here we go the list all the things with our class as an object to simply we have a class which is
a recipe and the object which is a cake.
So as I already said that class consists of the data and the method to insert the recipe.
We have some ingredients and after that we have some matters the ingredients are data and the metal
is a way to make the cake.
So when making something inside our glasses all we can say in that order is to be then the object will
also change.
So that's all about the glass as an object.
So now let's move to the other topic where we can see how to make the pluses and how to make the object
in Python.