Welcome to computer by do to do.
Today we are going to learn how to declare the classes and how to use the classes and objects.
So here I just open up our script and now I'm going to show you this index of class and we can say how
do the classes.
So here I just try to see it as class.
So the class is a key word.
So when we declare a function we use d s so that B F is a key word.
So Same here we have a class which is the class key word.
And after the keyword I just typed the name of the class which is a student.
So this woman is a name of the class.
So generally the name of the class is the standard form the capital letter.
So here I just write as in the typewriter after you just put a column to get in the class.
So this is the way to declare our class as we already know that inside a class with eight attributes
and matters which means that we age some ingredients and the matters which are used to big the cake.
So in python we cannot declare a variable.
We have to write the variable inside a special method that is any method the init method used to initialize
a variable instantly.
So now I'm going to in place of it method we can call it constructor also.
So here I going to define a function which is in it with never a new school.
After that I'll put cells.
And after that I'll put color to get inserted in it matter.
So here are you self-taught Nim which is equal to Alex.
So here we just create a variable which is the name of the student.
So now I'm going to play an object which used to call this all the matters so now I'm going to create
an object which is associated with the plus Asturian.
So here I just write as one after that and put equal to and after that equal to.
I just tried the name of the class which is a student.
So here you can see the S1 is the object of this student class.
So whatever we did inside the class it just goes to the S1.
So now here we just create a object S1 and now I'm going to print the name of this student which is
elex by using plain function print ESPERANDO name.
So now I'm going to run this model.
So here we get the result.
Alex So now I'm going to explain you what do the self here.
So self is all by we.
Or we can say the word that represent the class excelled.
So here I'm going to explain you with the object control-C.
Come on we here you can see we have to object which is S1 and S2.
So now I'm going to run this one again.
So here we get a result.
Alex and Alex two times.
So when we initialized variable which is the name itself which means that it will work with the current
object.
So when this object is used then as one is a for that and when this object used then it will look for
the s2.
So now I'm going to change this something like that which just as soon insert the cells.
I'm going to pass as one here.
Haven't read this MUNDIAL.
We get the result.
Self is not defined.
Sorry.
Here to write as one.
So here we get a result which is elex.
So here when we get a single object to the object it passes inside the method when we use a single object
and then we use our different different object which means that we have more than one object for a single
class.
Then we have to use our self keyword good or past the current object.
So selfie used to present the current object.
So as we know that every class has some action which is equal to method.
So now I'm going to create a method here.
So I just simply copied this word and put DTMF and now I'm going to call them in name the method which
is work.
So every students have some action equal to work which means that every student can walk around etc.
and said Here I just write self Hillsong
So here we just need all mattered in the class.
And now I'm going to in something which is my name is Alex.
So now I'm going to
call the method by using the object as standard work.
So now I'm going to run this more do you get those equal to is not defined so the split
hey we get the result which is equal to.
My name is Alex.
So this is the way to create a method in the class and this is the way to call this method using the
object.
And now I'm going to write here.
My name is
self-loading name.
So this safter name is a class variable which means that we can use this self-dual name anywhere in
this class
into this model.
We get a result my name is Alex.
Alex is a self-taught name.
So now let's move some other things which is self name and class story classes classes.
I'm going to copy the second name of order and put through times reduce self-taught classes and Sellersburg
mean them here I just write
classes and Leam.
So when we got a name here I read the boss of class here it will refer to these certain classes and
the surfer name.
So now I'm going to write to name which is X razored and class which is from 12.
Somehow when we put this model
we don't get any error.
Now I'm going to kill this by using self-taught names.
Sorry.
We're putting these server names names.
Self-taught memes.
So we need this more do we get the word which is name is not defined.
So names are idioms here.
So here we get a result which is my name is X Y Z.
So x is in which is equal to the last names.
And here are just plain dumb classes.
Now we need this model we get the result.
My name is X wizard alecks and 12.
So here we can see when the boxes are available in the class then the constructor is incidentally was
to separate the name and the separate classes itself.
So this method begins that constructor is used to initialize dto then say double plus.
So this all the variables are used anywhere in this class.
It means that these are class variable not a stance variable.
So now let's change something here.
I'm going to create another object equal to as two
extra dog walk and here I'm to pass something which is white X Wizard and you start eating.
So here we have two different object inside the object.
We have four different venues just exquisite.
Well why is it in Italy.
So with this model this first object is passes through this initialiser which is named in classes by
exquisite control and the eclipsing W which is ex-president.
Well I mean we deal with the second object then white X's.
Responses to these names.
And this it possible these classes to ascend with used to initialize are being assigned the object itself.
And now we get those are just equal to.
So here we get the result x x and y x Zed.
So we get a result different from the previous one because the two objects are used in two manners because
of the scent.
So then we use upthrust object the selfie refer to that and then we use a second object then central
deafer to this second object which is equal to as two.
So this is the way to use a cell.
And this is a way to create a class object and the method.
So that's all about the class as an object in Python.