Welcome to the party and to me today we're going to loan inheritance in Brighton.
Or we can say inheritance in the word inheritance means acquiring property from other sledged a good
example.
So here you can see there's a button and there's the sun.
So the sun is in some property from their parent which means that the parent is a base class and the
Son is derived class.
So when we did something inside of this class all we can say in class then the class can easily use
the property from the base class.
So the inheritance is used to acquire the property from the base class.
So there are two types of inheritance.
The first one is a single level inheritance and the second one is a multilevel inheritance.
So here you can see the child is inherited from a single base class which means that the base class
can be a father or mother.
So here we use a single level inheritance to acquire the property from the base class.
So now what is a multilevel inheritance.
Suppose we have a class which is our son and the Son is acquire a property from a base class which is
all father and mother.
So there is a base class which is father and mother.
So the son is acquired the property from the base classes which his father and mother.
This is called multi-role inheritance.
Now let's take a simple example to understand in doesn't bite.
So here I just opened up iTunes script and now I'm going to implement a simple example.
So here you have to write applause which is a key word.
And after that I like that even the clouds with you father after the input column and get inside the
glass.
And now I'm redefining of method which is last name
and instead the president says I'm the boss of cells.
I'm going to print W which is
my surname.
So here we have a betting class but we get a base class inside the base class we have a method which
is a last name.
Now I'm going to create a child class or we can say or B I love.
So here I will ride class or the alphabet alerts son that's for him and I'm going to declare a method
a B which is first name
ends are good but intensives put sealed up there and put color good in the method.
And now I'm going to simply bring the values of the concept string with just my first name.
So here you can see the read in class and after that there is a class.
So now how Pitre knows this is a draft class and this is very close to forbad you have to write the
name of the class from where you want to acquire the properties or reconsider but in class so far there
is a better class.
So here we have a class which is equal to father.
Now I'm going to an object because as one after the elder son and now I'm going to call the method which
is first name.
So here we just call the method which is partner from the sun or begins the second class.
Now when we do this more do we get the result.
My first inning.
So now I'm going to acquire the property which is the last name.
So here I just tried
one Dorte last name so when it is more do we get the result which is equal to my first name and surname.
So this my first name is coming from the charted class.
And this Sunday was coming from the class.
So this is the way to create a better class.
And the same class is called a single inheritance.
And now I'm going to get another glass to show the multilevel inheritance.
I just tried
a heavy heavy another class which is mother.
So have you ever take classes with his father mother and son.
So we have a two parent class which is father and mother.
So here I just write my surname to and now I'm going to do it again.
We get that Israel would just my first name and the son and now I'm going to edit something and said
oh so close.
And now I'm going to pass the mother class inside.
So close by using the name of the class.
So here I just like two classes which is a base class.
And now I'm going to simply write as one dark last name or thing or thing which is I think I picked
the name of the method which is last name ONE LAST NAME ONE.
So here read it and this Madill we get the results.
That is my surname too.
So you can see these results are coming from the base classes which is from father.
And this is from mother.
So this is a way to create a modular inheritance in Brighton.
You can add many things like when I copy and paste mother Sardi
grandmother pasta's base close to the class and third strike three.
And here I just start to hear and now I'm going to simply call this method by using the child class.
Well just last name to run it on is more do to good reason which is my son 3.
So these these are open from the base class and this first one is coming from the child class.
So these are all about in head heddes in Python.