Come to the right thing to do here today to discuss about our dictionary by our dictionary is only to
be done just like in list.
If you know what the Oxford Dictionary is or any dictionary is then what we see in the Oxford Dictionary
is that there is an outside world and these words have some meanings.
So by the time we have Oxford like dictionaries instead of words we have to show that we have revenue
and we
revenues are separated.
We them and yet there are so bitterly cold on.
The main difference between a dictionary and most peoples is that instead of being numbers that they
don't do anything much worse that when one group acts the item from the list was
made.
But in which they can use a pen just like Stroom character numbers.
So this is all about our study.
I'm just on to something.
So
I hope I shall do the.
So for that you're over I know some I don't.
So I'm going to because we don't have any.
I said This makes many are presumed And the reason for this is the first item here is 2007.
Hello.
So just to tell you something.
This is a new center.
When you put some item just to tell you.
And so this this is associated
with has been that there are so many items now.
I'm going to get it done so here I put the square back yard.
I could do something good.
Hello.
Hello my new which is associated with this game seven is all about the dictionary actually by time.