In this medium we're going to talk about some really didn't matter which I use the dictionary.
The first letter is a lengthy letter the Lennon-McCartney simply we don't know the number of item or
the number of people here which are exist in the dictionary.
So first we have to create our dictionary.
So here I created a dictionary as I know some believe in the dictionary.
And now I'm moving to the left of this dictionary.
I put in an instead the prentices and it put me in.
Which is a dictionary.
Here we are in this model and we get it for because we have four beer in this direction.
So these are all about.
Let me turn the next letter is.
My card.
The third is simply to the end of the envelope here which are existe and center dictionary.
So I heard a caller playing her.
No I'm going to read the dictionary.
So here being here is a
preserved in the dictionary because the items are clear using this clear weather.
So it is all about my kind of the next letter is the letter a copy of my third used to copy the item
which exist inside the dictionary.
So here I could get her duple variable B.
Now I'm going to copy the next day.
I don't see why we mattered which means that this dictionary is copying the new variable B.
And now I'm going to create the dictionary B.
So here it is.
So how do you get these are the same as you see in the dictionary.
Because this dictionary in its copy with a variable A B B G A B is a newly created dictionary having
the same value you we're still all about r.p.m.
the next time I don't either get ready or get my third return value for the given key if a key is in
north and then it will get done.
So for that I'm going to grade the value the time or the
propels it in you know we don't just want to do it here we get results.
I point to the the stream.
So seeing this proposal it key associated with this string.
I clearly now listing to them another key to
four letter than this one you begin going because it runs down.
Because this iPhone 4 is associated with this village rather than it is all about to get I heard the
national anthem and either I don't know I heard this and I third it on listo dictionary having a game
when do you know doubles form.
So from there we have a dictionary called me.
Now I'm going to simply print the items top items.
Here we get the result in the top of the form.
You see all the people appear in parentheses.
Which means that we use doubles and all the items are in the upper tier.
It is all about the items method.
The next one third is or isn't after the kids letter becomes our list of all the 11 there in the dictionary
that we have a dictionary called B and insert the dictionary so you will be ours and I'm going to simply
read all the Brennus in thought he might as I call this method get you right as now on this morning.
So here we get the result right on the nine and seven.
So these four items are key in this dictionary.
So is all about the method.
The next letter is update letter the other day.
My third I used to add two or more to the dictionary.
And after that you would get the updated results.
So here I go is having a variable B and B.
Now I'm going to get the dictionary using this dictionary will be for that.
We have to use it or abrogate my third and instead the president his I put my name b afraid that is
simply wrong.
The updated X to the it is a.
So here we get the result in the updated form because initially we have only 4 item in said dictionary.
And after that I updated the dictionary.
We have 8 items as we see in this output.
So these are all out.
Updated my third of the last 20 odd benches method.
The Vellis method simply written down all those values which are exist in the dictionary.
So I'm going to simply read all the values using this method.
Here is a dictionary and order and then is the other.
So I call the values method.
So here with this more do we get the result Hagar's Hegazy you get the all values from the dictionary
in.
These are all about Windows and these are all about the dictionary.
You can.