In this field you are going to talk about how to access how to update and how to deal the dictionary
now first how to access the venue in a dictionary.
For that you have to create our dictionary.
So I needed a dictionary and a signing for a new career in the dictionary.
So now I'm going to print the news using all this credit but I get into this crap and I get in 2007.
This is this.
So here I am on this model.
The good old iPhone which is searching the new iPhone is associated with this key and this is after
that grade.
This is Jim.
And now I'm going to turn the key 2000 mine which is these going on this month do we get the old iPhone
3G S which is just similar to this I'm not going to the key which is just an iPhone 4 which is just
similar to this.
The searching I from cool and has more to do with are just to dump them down because they didn't do
that do 2000 then associated with this is jinglin.
So you can use anything to add to the item from dictionary.
Now let's move to the next topic how to update the dictionary.
For that we have to get our dictionary.
So here I get a dictionary.
Signing for beer instead of the color is.
And now I'm going to update the game beer which is already exist in this dictionary.
So here I put it.
And I signed up 2007 and now I'm going to give different this to me just by time.
And after that it seemed to bring them up to the dictionary and there's more do we get the result as
we see the big havinga the new iPhone 3G which is similar to this.
Loving it.
And the next day we have to do as I can fool and lost.
You can see the 2007 heading for new which is a distinct item which means that the key to those timing
is did they put up another string.
So there is a way to update the game in the beer which is already exist in the dictionary.
So now I'm going to add a new beer in the dictionary.
Next I'm going to update the halting action which means that I'm going to add some beer and sceptered
dictionary.
So Third you have to assign a new key here.
I put 2000 11 which is a new key in this dictionary.
And I move to a different level word.
Now I'm going to do this more do.
Perhaps you can see those 11 is added in the dictionary.
So these are the two of the.
These are all about or updating the dictionary.
Let's move to the topic how to do the game from the dictionary.
For that to create a dictionary.
So here I created a dictionary and signing for give it to you and the dictionary.
And no I don't believe the e-mail we're using came in so that you beat me and my third and here the
name of the dictionary.
And that's quite a record.
I'm going to give the name of the game which is put on the seven and after that was simply the updated
diction and so here we get that is all.
So that being said the only basis on the team given new year with me is that the game of problem solving
is delayed.
There's a part of the game going to be using the game that is all about deleting the item from dictionary.