High everyone in this we are going to do an ASEAN which will incorporate the for loop range function.
And also IIF statement.
So in this example we are illustrating the combinational and as statement with the full statement that
search for prime numbers from 10 to 20.
So let's do that to.
And in order to do that first of all we have to iterate with we didn't get 20 for that.
Let's create a for loop for now.
Then doing
to iterate on the factors of the number.
Let's create a model for
do you know
that to determine the first factor.
Let's do
none more efficient.
I let's say that
right as I think the results do in East thinnish e.
Division I equal to zero then in order to calculate the second factor let's do g equals num divided
by
and
let's put in all the three values in fashion like
then DGT
equals
G.
Indu post indeed the
add in person each then you recess.
No I'm not.
I will not.
G and this person is d e's get replaced by name which is an integer.
That's why this person is D and this HD is get replaced by this I Indu and it's d again which is replaced
by this G
and after that if statement
do more to the next nimble and then an end statement would just know be as of this.
Q
Yes just three
Colma he's right.
So that's it.
Let's see if we go to the terminal in order to see the is.
So in the Downloads directory.
Well the file are you resides and Thuan python
files you look at here print in this fashion
and this underdo term we know that this technique was to do indeed fly then.
Is it brain work 12 equals doing to six inches of rain.
And so on up to 90 Mike it doesn't take this 20 since this range will take only values from 10 to 20
mins what we just made.
So that's all about range function for
keep watching and.