Heidi folks today the if statements in by then basically a statement has the ability to believe a conditions
based on which the behavior of the program.
Our goal our goal will be all that.
So this will this index up if statement of expression do something based on the resultant value of this
expression.
I mean whether it was true or false based on will continue to execute the next statement which was nothing
but do something or whatever the goal was here.
All right let's see an example of that interpreter
digital area will NSA do it.
All right.
Let's update this statement on the boat.
It
is
Biden initially executed this expression whether Hello exist in this string variable in tone what is
string theory will stream has a value of hello world in it and hence Biden has checked whether halo
exists in this hello world if it exits by then executive the next statement.
I mean the next line of code which was nothing but then hooray.
So that's what about using statements on particular string in Python.
Let's play this if statement on a list that.
Right now I'll play this statement on the claim list very
is
awesome.
So Biden initially has exhibited this expression and it has checked whether string hello x is in the
list variable.
I mean which has a do items in it.
Hello world.
And if that exits Biden has gone to exit the next statement which has been yes.
And then the result was yes that which was intended for us.
All right.
Let's see that example.
All right now in this statement or I play this statement on a Modica available
you have the output.
So this is a process of using IF statements and by the old times guys.