Hire one.
Now let's have a look at why then.
Ellis.
And as statements here I have created a new client statements.
We work in the same location
in this you will learn to read decisions in the program using Eve and live and as statements.
Decision making is required when we want to execute a call or leave a certain condition is satisfied.
Though if elif and statements are used by them for decision making
those is the syntax for if else and as conditions here the program evaluates the best expression and
then execute statements only if the best expression is true.
Otherwise it would check for the best expression of a list.
And this means the short form all ends if and if are the best expression is true or at least is get
executed and if not the control will go to the else statement and the else statement is the last one.
And if the condition is met then the body was and will be get executed and we have the flowchart of
the if elif and else statements over here as we see in the index itself.
The best description of if we could executed.
If so we also are testing whether the disposition is true.
If will be good exit conduct and if it is not true then the best description of Eliphaz evaluate and
check for whether it is true or false.
And if it is true value of Eliphaz get executed and if not the value of as is get executed and it will
be more clear then we do a program.
So let's go to the Sublime Text and let nothing equals three
and the first statement it is the east statement.
If they did then do.
This is the best expression andere this if conditions loyalty is identified by the indentation here
the in addition stops and we have a print expression here.
But it is positive.
And the if Baldie is terminated dirt while it sees a Norling the deadlock.
So here we have the as if that is our airlift condition over here.
Elif now equal to equal to zero gender linked
no means zero.
Here you might have far northeast YV using double equal to or we'll hear you single equal notation will
assign a value to a variable but the debit equal sign is used to compare the value.
So the last one ends here.
We can have
no expression is
not means negative
so that's it.
So just go to the terminal and clear the screen.
Then go to the all
Biden statements don't be very tender now.
Supposedly since we are given the three positive integer it is bring the vast numbers positive and if
we change this to minus 3 then save it and go to the terminal again.
Then run the code again.
There now is negative and the flow of program is like this.
The minus 3 is get assigned to the number number and the if condition checks whether the number is greater
than zero or not and nor do you want greater than zero.
So it will not print not supposedly And if condition is not also get satisfied so the else condition
is satisfied and thus it brings now is negative.
That's how the IIF Elif and else statements walk in Python and we can have the
same code like this here.
If Nauman greater than or equal to zero if not equal we call the zoo.
This yf is inside this.
If so it is nested IF ELSE condition and none is greater than Oracle.
So let's do this 2 3 again and see if it.
So now the condition is East condition is true.
It is greater than zero and now it will check for it.
No equally will do then it will print 0 and if else then it will print.
It is a positive number.
Since we are using all by then.
2.7.
We don't need this brackets.
That's one of the difference between by the dewpoint 7 and by the do 3.
So let's run this call again.
Then go to the terminal and again then it is positive number.
That's the IIF Elif and Else statement.
By that that's all for now.
Keep watching.
Thank you.