Welcome to the right into doing today we are going to talk about mood control statements in Python so
you can call Instagram's are a blatant statement know continuing statement.
So what is the biggest regret.
Biggest J-20 simply used to edit the loop or you can say that you're simply used to break the loo.
After that it will go to the next line or next statement.
So this is all out to make a statement.
So now let us understand a big statement to a simple program here opened up our offensive and now I'm
using a closed loop to understand the biggest Dittman
yet strangely the simple character.
So now I initially print simple for loop to get the result from Asked to Z which is a simple for loop
result.
Now what happened when I put a great question mark this in said this bording that I lose if condition.
So here you can see this is the if condition for data structure and condition.
So now after and after the condition and put the second statement
which is a hello.
It was simply Brinda.
Hello.
So now if maybe it would be quick do I.
Which means that when a variable goes to the addition of.
I inserted this character it will simply break the loop and Worcester next line or to that next statement
which is this the statement.
So now I run this group name.
Now you can see what happened.
So here you can see we could simply did the loop after the architecture which means that when a variable
goes to the iPod you can simply break the new one goes to the next line which is a Hello.
So now I change the character in this video book.
So now you can see they did not get inside this character so to simply put in the condition because
if condition is not satisfied so it will simply print that as condition as condition as condition is
simply a string.
After that it was simply the slip in the next statement.
Now I like good this program so I can see there isn't no big things at this result so it will simply
print Renda from S to Z.
After that it will print the second line.
So this is all about to make a statement.
So now what do you want.
Granted your statement continued statement is simply used to skip the loop and goes to the next iteration.
Here I see you do good to the next iteration.
Not in the next line so it will simply skip the loop and goes to the next iteration.
So this is all about continuous check statement.
I didn't understand through a simple example here.
I again open a potential and now I am.
I've been using a for loop to understand a continuous statement
where again a string is a character
I'm against celebrity but simply for very good.
Those are the Jersey which is simple for liberty.
Now why pick Brenneman I put in a statement and he said this portaloo of course that I used to
so Hedican see if nobody ever goes to the position of I'm in this esteem it will simply skip the loop.
Or we can say that it will simply escape the character and go to the next edition.
And after that we do the deed.
So this is the continue side of this for look at that and put in a statement after the current you know
new
do the hello could disprove them.
So here we can get Brazil hit again soon.
No I didn't said this reserve which means there is a.
And after that it goes to an energy of in the loop was completed.
It will goes to the next line.
So this is all about the continuous treatment.